<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Confluence</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 05:41:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.4.2</generator>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. G. Rajagopal</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1327</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1327#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 06:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1327</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[At the outset, let me congratulate you and your esteemed institution for hosting CONFLUENCE for the third year in succession. Thanks very much for asking me to be a part of the event this year also. CONFLUENCE is indeed an innovative, invigorating meeting of minds from India and overseas. I have always enjoyed interacting with&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">At the outset, let me congratulate you and your esteemed institution for hosting CONFLUENCE for the third year in succession. Thanks very much for asking me to be a part of the event this year also.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">CONFLUENCE is indeed an innovative, invigorating meeting of minds from India and overseas.</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: justify;">I have always enjoyed interacting with the brilliant presenters, and I am looking forward to a similar experience at the forthcoming seminar too.</p>
</blockquote>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The theme of this year’s seminar opens up interesting possibilities for discussion. TESL is itself undergoing an upheaval of sorts given the widely varied ELT contexts the world over, and it should be interesting to see how this CONFLUENCE shapes itself up with the ‘Global Perspective’ you have proposed as the theme this year.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">While wishing the seminar every success, I look forward to an academically refreshing time at CONFLUENCE once again.</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-rajagopal.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1328" title="dr-rajagopal" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-rajagopal.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. G. Rajagopal</strong><br />
Professor, Department of ESL Studies<br />
School of English Language Education<br />
English and Foreign Languages University<br />
Hyderabad, India</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="text-align: justify;">Dr. G. Rajagopal, a member of the National Academic Advisory Committee of the Government of India, has practically been a mentor for Confluence.  He is a Professor at the School of English Language Education in The English and Foreign Languages University (TEFLU), Hyderabad. He has a wide teaching experience in India and overseas and specializes in TESL/TEFL, ESP/EAP/EOP, Phonetics, and Spoken English.  An academic of high repute, he serves on many Boards of Studies in English of various universities and has several publications to his credit.  He has also developed a Bilingual Reading Method for Kannada students using their L1 knowledge as a resource.  Dr. Rajagopal is also very well known for his fabulous lectures and workshops on various aspects of ESL.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1327</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. Amir Mehdavi Zafarghandi</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1298</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1298#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 20:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1298</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[First and foremost, I would like to welcome all participants and attendees to 2012 Annual Confluence of Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology, Nagpur, Maharashtra, India. It has been great privilege and enormous pleasure to serve Confluence as a participant as well as a member of the editorial board. At Confluence here we are&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First and foremost, I would like to welcome all participants and attendees to 2012 Annual Confluence of Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology, Nagpur, Maharashtra, India. It has been great privilege and enormous pleasure to serve Confluence as a participant as well as a member of the editorial board. At Confluence here we are a community of faculty, staff, scholars, researchers and research students, nationally and internationally. We all share a restless desire for learning, teaching, excellence and professionalism.</p>
<p>Similar to last years, this year Confluence covers a variety of interesting themes in Teaching of ESL: A Global Perspective. Without a doubt, exploring these subjects via professional presentations and follow-up discussions will help Confluence continue to move into the ranks of most outstanding seminars in addition to offering us invaluable insights on how to better educate our students to explore their possibilities and achieve their potential.</p>
<blockquote><p>For this wonderful Confluence in 2010 and 2011, together, we have made important accomplishments.</p></blockquote>
<p>This year, we will continue our many efforts to make Confluence grow more strongly and meaningfully, I appreciate your attendance, Participation, support, and cooperation.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dr.-Amir-Mahdavi-Zafarghandi.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1299" title="Dr.-Amir-Mahdavi-Zafarghandi" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dr.-Amir-Mahdavi-Zafarghandi.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. Amir Mehdavi Zafarghandi</strong><br />
English Department<br />
Faculty of Humanities<br />
University of Guilan</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1298</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. Ronnie Goodwin</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1295</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1295#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 20:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1295</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It is a great honor to be associated with Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology in Nagpur, India. This year&#8217;s Third Annual International Seminar “Confluence&#8221; seminar titled, Teaching of ESL: A Global Perspective brings teachers from around the world to discuss and exchange ideas on how to better address the problems of English learners&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is a great honor to be associated with Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology in Nagpur, India. This year&#8217;s Third Annual International Seminar “Confluence&#8221; seminar titled, Teaching of ESL: A Global Perspective brings teachers from around the world to discuss and exchange ideas on how to better address the problems of English learners and teachers in the technical field.</p>
<p>We, as teachers, need to continue sharing the problems that we face in the classroom, as well as our teaching practices, to help one another learn invaluable insights into strategies that will help each of us to overcome barriers, to lower our &#8220;affective filter&#8221; and to gain a better understanding on how we can be more creative in designing and delivering lessons to our students so that they will become a strong fluid English voice in our global world.</p>
<p>The Confluence seminar will do this, and it is to this determination and dedication that I support the conference and its mission. I feel certain that all who participate will gain the awareness needed to be a stronger practitioner in the realm of ESL teaching, and all who participate will have a wonderful time associating with fellow colleagues from all around the world.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-ronnie-goodwin.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1303" title="dr-ronnie-goodwin" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-ronnie-goodwin.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. Ronnie Goodwin</strong><br />
Gulf University for Science and Technology</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1295</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. Pankaj Chande</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1290</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1290#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 20:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1290</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It is a matter of happiness that the third ‘Annual International Seminar on Teaching ESL: A Global Perspective’ is being organized at Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology. Though this is an era of knowledge and technology, the language component in academics and social interaction is equally important. English being an international language, the&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is a matter of happiness that the third ‘Annual International Seminar on Teaching ESL: A Global Perspective’ is being organized at Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology. Though this is an era of knowledge and technology, the language component in academics and social interaction is equally important.</p>
<p>English being an international language, the thought churning deliberations in this seminar about its status as a second language will definitely benefit students who prefer English as a language of communication and expression.</p>
<p>I hope that the deliberations will be fruitful and direction-giving for the proper usage of this language in this era of SMS communication.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dr-Pankaj-Chande.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1291" title="Dr-Pankaj-Chande" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dr-Pankaj-Chande.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. Pankaj Chande</strong><br />
Vice Chancellor<br />
Kavi Kulguru Kalidas Sanskrit University</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1290</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. Nasrin Shokrpour</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1284</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1284#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 20:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1284</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It is my sincere pleasure to welcome you all to the international seminar on ‘Innovations in Language Teaching in Technical Education’, organized by the Department of Basic Sciences and Humanities of the Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering &#38; Technology. On behalf of the organizing committee, I would like to welcome all of you to the&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is my sincere pleasure to welcome you all to the international seminar on ‘Innovations in Language Teaching in Technical Education’, organized by the Department of Basic Sciences and Humanities of the Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering &amp; Technology.</p>
<p>On behalf of the organizing committee, I would like to welcome all of you to the college. This conference is organized with the aim of promoting collaboration between researchers in the fields of EFL methodology, introduction of technology in teaching and learning English, language skills and global competitiveness, and finally gathering designs to revise the curriculum.</p>
<p>We hope that this conference will contribute to the advancement of research in FL learning and teaching and, ultimately, to the enhancement of the learners&#8217; success.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dr.-Nasrin-Shokrpour.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1285" title="Dr.-Nasrin-Shokrpour" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dr.-Nasrin-Shokrpour.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. Nasrin Shokrpour<br />
</strong>Associate Professor in Applied Linguistics<br />
and Vice Dean for Educational Affairs<br />
in the Faculty of Paramedical Sciences<br />
Shiraz University of Medical Sciences</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1284</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Mr. Do Ba Quy</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1273</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1273#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 18:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1273</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I would like to wish Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology a successful seminar with new insights into the teaching of languages in technical education and do hope that Confluence will mark the beginning of many other fruitful seminars at the College in the years to come. Best wishes to you all. Do Ba&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">I would like to wish Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology a successful seminar with new insights into the teaching of languages in technical education and do hope that Confluence will mark the beginning of many other fruitful seminars at the College in the years to come.</p>
<p>Best wishes to you all.</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/do-ba-quy.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1274" title="do-ba-quy" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/do-ba-quy.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Do Ba Quy<br />
</strong>Faculty of Post-Graduate Studies<br />
University of Languages and International Studies<br />
Vietnam National University, Hanoi<br />
Pham Van Dong Road, Cau Giay District, Hanoi, Vietnam</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1273</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. Amol Padwad</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1268</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1268#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1268</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I am extremely glad to see that the Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology is organising an international conference on “Innovations in Language Teaching and Technical Education”. The College has chosen a very relevant theme for consideration and has also taken a brave step in trying to get together academics and practitioners from different&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">I am extremely glad to see that the Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology is organising an international conference on “Innovations in Language Teaching and Technical Education”. The College has chosen a very relevant theme for consideration and has also taken a brave step in trying to get together academics and practitioners from different parts of India and from abroad to share their ideas, experiences and expertise.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">I believe this seminar is the first of its kind in the Vidarbha region and must congratulate the TGP College of Engineering and Technology for providing a forum for interaction and exchange to the teachers of professional courses.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">I am sure this event will contribute significantly to the individual enrichment of the participants and also to the enhancement of quality in the teaching-learning process in general. I am also glad and honoured to be a part of this endeavour.</p>
<p>I wish the seminar great success!</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-amol-padwad.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1269" title="dr-amol-padwad" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-amol-padwad.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. Amol Padwad<br />
</strong>National President<br />
English Language Teachers’ Association of India</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1268</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Yvonne M. Esperas</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1260</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1260#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 17:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1260</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I commend the organizers of this international conference themed “Teaching and Learning of English as a Second Language in Technical Education: Overcoming the Odds”. The theme is very timely and responsive to the global concerns. Always we are confronted with the quest to improve our quality of life. Also we are challenged to succeed in&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">I commend the organizers of this international conference themed “Teaching and Learning of English as a Second Language in Technical Education: Overcoming the Odds”. The theme is very timely and responsive to the global concerns. Always we are confronted with the quest to improve our quality of life. Also we are challenged to succeed in the international arena, and what essential tool could there be but English, an international language.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Learning another language, such as English, is like building a bridge that enables us to reach out to others and cross boundaries. It is an important tool to communicate. It helps us build cultural and economic ties with other nations and establish power. Language, therefore, is an indispensable tool for development.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Specifically, English language is instrumental for learners to master technical education. It allows them to concretize invention or innovation ideas, despite the most specialized nature of technical data. Thus, they are able to express them in the most comprehensible manner, thereby breaking communication blocks. When learners comprehend better the structure of technical information, they become equipped with skills to face the challenges of the times and to welcome and even create opportunities in this internationally competitive milieu. This is where learners derive power. When they become linguistically proficient, there is no reason why they cannot achieve their goals, maximize their potentials as productive citizens, and participate fully in the local and global communities.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Let this conference be an encouragement to all educators to seek better remedies to learning problems. Let us all continue to enhance teaching strategies that center on the learners, so that these students will master the much needed linguistic skills. Indeed, if learning a language is like building a bridge, let us make its foundation strong and reliable enough to withstand all weathers.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/yvonne_esperas.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1266" title="yvonne_esperas" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/yvonne_esperas.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a><br />
<strong>Yvonne M. Esperas</strong><br />
Head, Humanities Department<br />
Philippine Science High School<br />
Eastern Visayas Campus</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1260</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Dr. Ved Prakash Mishra</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1331</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1331#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 07:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=1331</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It gives me immense pleasure and satisfaction to note that the Third Annual International Conference on Teaching of ESL: A Global Perspective has been scheduled by the Department of Basic Sciences and Humanities, Tusliramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology, Nagpur, on Feb 24 – 25, 2012. It has been rightly titled as ‘Confluence’, which&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">It gives me immense pleasure and satisfaction to note that the Third Annual International Conference on Teaching of ESL: A Global Perspective has been scheduled by the Department of Basic Sciences and Humanities, Tusliramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Technology, Nagpur, on Feb 24 – 25, 2012.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">It has been rightly titled as ‘Confluence’, which genuinely brings out the contours and directions in which the conference is expected to shape itself. I am sure the conference is bound to address the problems of English teachers and learners in all their manifestation. As a matter of fact, the conference per se is bound to provide a meaningful platform, which will emerge as an edifice for not only unloading the problems that English learners and teachers face, but also in generating solutions to the very problems out of the learned deliberations and discussions that would take place in the form of free-flowing exchange of ideas.</p>
<blockquote><p>It is bound to give a fillip to the conventional pedagogy of teaching of English and definitely prove to be the focal point of the creation of a network of the English teachers duly catalyzed by their immaculate expertise and learned experience.</p></blockquote>
<p style="text-align: justify;">I have no hesitation in candidly putting across that a great void in this arena will be decisively filled up by the scheduled conference. My good wishes for its all round success.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-mishra.jpg"><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-1332" title="dr-mishra" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/dr-mishra.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /></a>Dr. Ved Prakash Mishra</strong><br />
Pro-Chancellor<br />
Datta Meghe Institute of Medical Sciences (Deemed University)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=1331</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Prof. Anne Burns</title>
		<link>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=121</link>
		<comments>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?p=121#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 18:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>confluence-admin</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Messages from Guests]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abha College of Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Confluence 2011]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prof. Anne Burns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TGP-CET]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://itis.parkerandkent.com/itis/?p=121</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It is a great honour to be invited to be associated with the Annual International Conference organized by the Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Abha College of Engineering at Nagpur, Maharashtra, India. The theme of the conference, Teaching and Learning of ESL in Technical Education: Overcoming the Odds touches on some of the most&#8230;]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="70" height="70" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/prof-anne-burns-70x70.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="prof-anne-burns" title="prof-anne-burns" /><p>It is a great honour to be invited to be associated with the Annual International Conference organized by the Tulsiramji Gaikwad-Patil College of Engineering and Abha College of Engineering at Nagpur, Maharashtra, India.</p>
<p>The theme of the conference, Teaching and Learning of ESL in Technical Education: Overcoming the Odds touches on some of the most important issues and challenges for education in today&#8217;s world as the use of English expands internationally. Gaining competence in English as a second language is now an important attribute for the technical and business field as well as for further education.</p>
<blockquote><p>I give my full support to the conference organizers and congratulate them on their plans for this event.</p></blockquote>
<p>I am confident that all the conference participants will enjoy a stimulating and challenging time and a wonderful opportunity to exchange ideas with colleagues from different parts of India and other countries.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft" title="prof-anne-burns" src="http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/prof-anne-burns.jpg" alt="" width="163" height="163" /><br />
<strong>Prof. Anne Burns</strong><br />
University of New South Wales Sydney, Australia.<br />
<a href="http://www.professoranneburns.com" target="_blank">www.professoranneburns.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.confluenceindia.co.in/?feed=rss2&#038;p=121</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
